{"instructions": ["You will be listening to a sound beep that starts from either your left side or the right side and then jumps to the other side. <p></p>Your task is to click on either <strong>left to right</strong> or <strong>right to left</strong> to indicate the moving direction", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to start the first sound beep."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "To begin, make sure you are in a quiet room and wearing your <strong>wired</strong> head/earphones. Let us adjust the volume before starting the test.<p> Click <strong>Continue</strong> to proceed.</p>", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Now adjust your computer volume up to a comfortable (but not too loud) level.", "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/volume.wav", "choices": ["I have adjusted the volume, let's continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "The headphones are usually marked as left/right to indicate which ear they are for. Did you make sure the right headphone is in your right ear, and the left headphone is in your left ear? It is very important for making the correct decisions.", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_czS59831XIzhO1r0.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_xqjNt7ETaLJYO23j.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_XdysTgXWHpeMbdiB.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_2_1EdtNWrEYKHuzXvC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_QJOEyDez8WTVU0V8.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_yEqc8TjjRxeziX5a.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_2_Qp0sbfXSWMZczpD2.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_LbjZmZuPdTE6rxh7.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_fSFuUZpHAjL6g3IA.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_pBHvV2TzLNhEtJ6A.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_55wqWFIQf26f04aG.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_2_xOVJNr0ANZqyIBfU.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_Ac8G4x2p43yMJ3na.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_2_opNsZ26yXjMRfG3q.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/demo/3.2dB_1_0EjoOIsMSrzwWi3r.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}]}